Guide to the James Lapine Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
James Lapine papers
1974-2008
YCAL MSS 715
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
56.84
(63 boxes)
The papers consist of material created and accumulated by James Lapine in the course of his creative and professional activities as a playwright and director. Material includes scripts, production notes and files, correspondence, writings, printed material, audiovisual material, and photographs documenting Lapine's work on individual plays and productions, and the process of bringing a play or musical to the stage.
Lapine, James, 1949-
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from George Robert Minkoff Inc. on the Adele Gutman Nathan Theatrical Collection Fund, 2006, and gift of James Lapine, 2009.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 47-50 and 63 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 53 and 61 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
James Lapine (1949- )
James Lapine is an American playwright and director. He was born in Mansfield, Ohio, studied at the California Institute of the Arts, and worked at the Yale University School of Drama. Lapine collaborated, as writer and director, on several musicals with Stephen Sondheim, including Sunday in the Park with George (1984), Into the Woods (1987), and Passion (1994). His other directorial credits include Falsettos (1992), for which he also wrote the libretto, The Diary of Anne Frank (1997), Golden Child (1998), Der Glockner von Notre Dame (1999), Dirty Blonde (2000), and The 25th Annual Putnam County Spelling Bee (2005). His plays include Table Setting (1978), Twelve Dreams (1978), Luck, Pluck, and Virtue (1994), The Moment When (2000), and Fran's Bed (2005).
Scope and Contents
The papers consist of material created and accumulated by James Lapine in the course of his creative and professional activities as a playwright and director. Material includes scripts, production notes and files, correspondence, writings, printed material, audiovisual material, and photographs documenting Lapine's work on individual plays and productions, and the process of bringing a play or musical to the stage.
Arrangement
Organized into two groupings: I. May 2006 Acquisition. II. January 2009 Acquisition.
Material within this collection has been organized by acquisition reflecting the fact that the collection has been acquired in increments over time. Researchers should note that material within each acquisition overlaps with/or relates to material found in other acquisitions. For instance, scripts and production files can be found in both groupings. In order to locate all relevant material within this collection, researchers will need to consult each acquisition described in the Collection Contents section. Researchers should also note that similar material can be arranged differently in each acquisition, depending on how the material was organized when it was received by the library.
American drama -- 20th Century; American drama -- 21st century; Dramatists, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Dramatists, American -- 21st century -- Archives; Theater -- United States; Audiocassettes -- United States -- 20th Century; Audiovisual materials -- United States -- 20th Century; Born digital -- United States -- 20th Century; Electronic documents -- United States -- 20th Century; Photographs -- United States -- 20th Century; Sound recordings -- United States -- 20th Century; Videocassettes -- United States -- 20th Century; Dramatists, American -- 20th Century; Dramatists, American -- 21st century; Lapine, James, 1949-
- May 2006 Acquisition, 1974-2006; Series I; 49.25; (53 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Organized under five headings: Play Files, Assorted Scripts, Other Papers, Audiovisual Material, and Electronic Media.
  Scope and Contents
  This group of material contains scripts, production notes, audiocassettes, videocassettes, photographs, slides, computer disks, and other papers relating to James Lapine and his work.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 47-50 (audiovisual material): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Box 53 (computer disks): Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  General note
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 856
  - Play Files
    Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - The Diary of Anne Frank
      - "The Diary of Anne Frank" by Frances Goodrich and Albert Hackett, undated; 2 (Box 1)
      - Photocopied pictures, undated (Box 1)
      - "The Publicity Office", 1997 (Box 1)
      - "The Diary of Anne Frank" [script], undated (Box 1)
      - Press, 1998 (Box 1)
      - Miscellaneous [from Publicity office], 1997-1998; 2 (Box 1)
      - Script Revisions, 1997 (Box 1)
      - Research materials, 1997 (Box 1)
      - Schedule, 1997 (Box 1)
      - House seats, 1997-1998 (Box 1)
      - Miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 1)
      - Performance reports, 1997-1998 (Box 1)
      - Reading, 1996 (Box 1)
      - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 1)
      - Anne Frank, 1997-1998; 2 (Box 1)
      - Amsterdam trip, 1997 (Box 1)
      - Casting, 1997-1998 (Box 1)
      - Contact Sheets, 1997-1998 (Box 1)
      - Contracts, 1995-1998 (Box 1)
      - Expenses, 1997-1998 (Box 1)
      - [Script with notes: Act One], 1997 Aug 5 (Box 1)
      - [Act One], 1997 Aug 10 (Box 1)
      - Act II, 1997 (Box 1)
      - [Misc], 1996 (Box 1)
      - The Netherlands and Nazi Germany, by Louis de Jung [photocopy of book], undated (Box 1)
      - Anne Frank, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Dirty Blonde
      - Wildcard material (not used), 1994 Nov 24 (Box 2)
      - Tough Girl calling script, 1998 Jul 25 (Box 2)
      - Tough Girl script, 1998 Aug 15 (Box 2)
      - Script, 1999 Aug 10 (Box 2)
      - Gareth notes and old pages, 1999 Nov (Box 2)
      - Script first New York Theatre Workshop rehearsal, 1999 Nov 9 (Box 2)
      - Partial script with revisions, 1999 Dec 1 (Box 2)
      - New York Theatre Workshop master script, 2000 Jan 15 (Box 2)
      - Helen Hayes production, 2000 Nov 14 (Box 2)
      - Script, first rehearsal Helen Hayes, 2000 Mar 9 (Box 2)
      - Outdated script pages, 1999 (Box 2)
      - Blown Sideways script, 1998 Nov 12 (Box 2)
      - Rewrite memos and note cards, 1999 (Box 2)
      - Pages never put in, 1999 (Box 2)
      - Research, 1996-1998 (Box 2)
      - Scene breakdown, 1998 (Box 2)
      - Press, 2000 (Box 2)
      - Cut music, 1999 (Box 2)
      - Legal rights, 1999 (Box 2)
      - Casting, 2000-2001 (Box 3)
      - Budget, 1998-2000 (Box 3)
      - Schedule, 1999-2001 (Box 3)
      - New York Theatre Workshop production, 2000 Jan 7 (Box 3)
      - New York Theatre Workshop Archives, 1999-2000 (Box 3)
      - Correspondence, 1997-2004 (Box 3)
      - London correspondence, 2004 (Box 3)
      - London reviews, 2004 (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous, 1998-2000 (Box 3)
      - The Wit and Wisdom of Mae West, undated (Box 3)
      - Pocket [note cards], undated (Box 3)
      - Pocket, 1998-2002; 3 (Box 3)
    - Elmer Gantry
      - Contracts, 1996 (Box 4)
      - Contact sheets, 1996 (Box 4)
      - Casting, 1996 (Box 4)
      - Casting Light, 1996 (Box 4)
      - Budget, 1996 (Box 4)
      - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 4)
      - Financials, 1996 (Box 4)
      - Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 4)
      - Ford Theatre production, 1995-1996 (Box 4)
      - 1988 and 1996 May 1, 1988, 1996 (Box 4)
      - 1995 Oct 27 and 1996 Apr 10, 1995, 1996 (Box 4)
      - 1996 Apr 16 and 1996 Apr 29 (Box 4)
      - 1996 Jun 11 and 1996 Jul 2 (Box 4)
      - 1996 Aug 5 (Box 4)
      - 1996 Sep 5 and notes, 2 (Box 4)
      - 1996 Sep 9 of Lapine notes (Box 4)
      - Music and Lyrics, 1996 (Box 4)
      - 1996 Sep 11 (Box 4)
      - 1996 Sep 13 with Lapine notes (Box 4)
    - Falsettos
      - Production script, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
      - Fox 2000, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
      - Old pages movie, undated (Box 5)
      - Movie receipts, 1993-1994 (Box 5)
      - Screenplay 2nd draft, undated (Box 5)
      - Falsettos, 1993-1995; 2 (Box 5)
      - 1994 Jun (Box 5)
      - Falsettos, 1994; 9 (Box 5)
      - Falsettos, 1992-1994; 4 (Box 5)
    - Faust
      - Randy Newman misc, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Research, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - 1991 Nov 15, 2 (Box 6)
      - Final first draft, 1992 Apr 20 (Box 6)
      - 1994 Nov 17 (Box 6)
      - Office copy, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Performance draft (most recent), 1994 Dec 1 (Box 6)
      - Research, undated; 3 (Box 6)
    - Faust script revision, production files
      - Act One Scene 1, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Act One Scene 2, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Act One Scene 3, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Act One Scene 4, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Act One Scene 5, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Act One Scene 6, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Act Two Scene 1, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Act Two Scene 2, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Act Two Scene 3, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Act Two Scene 4, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Act Two Scene 5, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Act Two Scene 6, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Act Two Scene 7, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Act Two Scene 8, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Lapine notes for rewrite, 1991 Nov 15 (Box 6)
      - Script revision and producer files, 1994 (Box 6)
      - Lapine's final notes pre-printing, 1994 Nov 17 (Box 6)
      - 1994 Nov 17 (Box 6)
      - G Hendee's with notes, 1994 Nov 7 (Box 7)
      - J Wagner's with notes, 1994 Nov 7 (Box 7)
      - Breakdowns, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
      - Budget, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Casting, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Contracts, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Misc, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Program, 1994 (Box 7)
      - 1994 Nov 7 (Box 7)
      - 1994 Nov 4 (Box 7)
      - 1994 Oct 4 - Nov 11 "first input' with notes (Box 7)
      - 1994 Oct 4 with Notes (Box 7)
      - 1991 Nov 15, 3 (Box 7)
      - 1992 Apr 20 (Box 7)
    - Faust scripts, supervisor's files, production records
      - Best Little Girl, undated (Box 8)
      - Bleeding, undated (Box 8)
      - Bless the Children of the World, undated (Box 8)
      - Can't Keep a Good Man Down, undated (Box 8)
      - My Hero, undated (Box 8)
      - Eastertime, undated (Box 8)
      - Feels Like Home, undated (Box 8)
      - Gainesville, FL, undated (Box 8)
      - Glory Train, undated (Box 8)
      - Heaven/Hell Stings, undated (Box 8)
      - How Great Our Lord, undated (Box 8)
      - I Gotta Be Your Man, undated (Box 8)
      - It Was Beautiful, undated (Box 8)
      - Life Has Been Good to Me, undated (Box 8)
      - Little Island, undated (Box 8)
      - March of the Protestants, undated (Box 8)
      - The Man, undated (Box 8)
      - Northern Boy, undated (Box 8)
      - Pass On Over, undated (Box 8)
      - Relax, Enjoy Yourself, undated (Box 8)
      - Sandman's Coming, undated (Box 8)
      - When Love is in the Air, undated (Box 8)
      - Programs, undated (Box 8)
    - Golden Child
      - [review], 1996-1997; 2 (Box 8)
      - Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 8)
      - House Seats, 1998 (Box 8)
      - Contracts, 1996-1998 (Box 8)
      - Contact Sheets, 1997-1998 (Box 8)
      - Casting, 1996-1997 (Box 8)
      - Golden Child, 1997-1998 (Box 8)
      - Press, 1998 (Box 8)
      - Performance reports, 1998 (Box 8)
      - Golden Child and schedules, 1998 (Box 8)
      - Director's Script, 1997 (Box 8)
      - Golden Child, 1996-1998; 6 (Box 9)
    - Hunchback ( Der Glockner von Notre Dame )
      - [Correspondence], 1997-2000 (Box 9)
      - Old Pages Act 1, 1998 (Box 9)
      - Old Pages Act 2, 1998 (Box 9)
      - Hunchback, undated (Box 9)
      - Effects, 1999 (Box 9)
      - Cast Resumes, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
      - Design meeting, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
      - Readings, 1997-1998 (Box 9)
      - Music, undated (Box 9)
      - James breakdown, 1997 (Box 9)
      - Schedule, 1997-1999 (Box 10)
      - German Press, 1998 (Box 10)
      - Hunchback - research, 1997 (Box 10)
      - Blocking Notes, undated (Box 10)
      - Script Rewrite Memos, 1998 (Box 10)
      - Script, 1999 Jun (Box 10)
      - Hunchback, 1998-1999; 5 (Box 10)
      - Director's Script, 1999 (Box 10)
      - Stage Version, 1997-1998; 2 (Box 10)
      - Film Script, 1995 (Box 10)
      - Old Pages, 1999 Mar 1 (Box 10)
      - Hunchback Old Pages, 1998 (Box 11)
      - Hunchback Memos AM TSS, 1997-1998 (Box 11)
    - Into the Woods, 1985-1990; 16 (Box 11)
    - Into the Woods, 1985-2004; 16 (Box 12)
    - Into the Woods, 1986-2001; 15 (Box 13)
    - Into the Woods, 1986-2002; 12 (Box 14)
    - Luck, Pluck, and Virtue
      - Miscellaneous, 1978-1993; 5 (Box 14)
      - Score, La Jolla production, 1993 Aug (Box 15)
      - La Jolla rewrite, 1993 (Box 15)
      - Rewrites/notes, 1993 (Box 15)
      - Music and lyrics, 1993-1995; 3 (Box 15)
      - Miscellaneous, 1993; 3 (Box 15)
      - A Cool Million, novel, undated (Box 15)
      - Research, undated (Box 15)
      - Casting, 1995 (Box 15)
      - La Jolla production, 1992-1994 (Box 15)
      - Atlantic budget, 1995 (Box 15)
      - Press reviews, 1995 (Box 15)
      - Notes, 1993-1994 (Box 16)
      - Schedules, 1995 (Box 16)
      - Script breakdowns, 1993 (Box 16)
      - Theatre, 1994 (Box 16)
      - JL early notebook, undated (Box 16)
      - Michael Starobin, 1994 (Box 16)
      - Sound, 1994 (Box 16)
      - Atlantic Legal/contract, 1994-1995 (Box 16)
      - La Jolla review/press pictures, 1993 (Box 16)
      - Playbills, 1993; 3 (Box 16)
      - Performance, 1995 Jul 4 (Box 17)
      - Rehearsal, 1995 Mar 14 (Box 17)
      - Rehearsal, 1995 Nov 3 (Box 17)
      - Rehearsal, 1995 Oct 3 (Box 17)
      - Rehearsal, 1995 Mar 3 (Box 17)
      - 2/27-3/25/95 Script changes/rewrites, 1995 (Box 17)
      - Rehearsal, 1995 Feb 25 (Box 17)
      - Master, 1995 Jan 16 (Box 17)
      - Revised, 1995 Nov 6 (Box 17)
      - Master, 1994 Nov 4 (Box 17)
      - Performance, 1993 Aug 21 (Box 17)
      - Fourth draft, 1993 Jul 15 (Box 17)
      - Rehearsal, 1993 Jul 2 (Box 17)
      - 2nd draft, 1991 Nov 8 (Box 17)
      - 3rd draft, 1993 Jun 22 (Box 17)
      - Miscellaenous, 1993; 3 (Box 17)
    - The Moment When
      - Miscellaneous pulled pages, 2000 (Box 18)
      - Press, correspondence, contact sheets, contracts, 1996-2000 (Box 18)
      - Financial, house casts, retired pages, 2000-2001 (Box 18)
      - Scripts, 1997-2002; 13 (Box 18)
    - Merrily We Roll Along, 1985; 3 (Box 19)
    - Mrs. Caliban
      - Contracts, correspondence, notes, undated (Box 19)
      - Screenplays, related material, 1995-1996; 9 (Box 19)
      - Screenplays, related material, 1995; 2 (Box 19)
    - Muscle
      - Scripts, related papers, 1995-1996; 20 (Box 20)
      - Muscle, 1992-2001; 7 (Box 21)
      - Scripts, 2001; 5 (Box 21)
      - Budget, undated (Box 21)
      - Muscle, 2001 (Box 21)
      - Retired pages, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Director's scripts, 1995; 2 (Box 21)
      - Lapine's old pages, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Scripts, 1995; 6 (Box 22)
      - Readings, 1995; 8 (Box 23)
      - Daily notes, 1995 (Box 23)
      - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 23)
      - Invoices, 1995 (Box 23)
      - Lyrics, 1995-1996 (Box 23)
      - [empty folder], undated (Box 23)
      - Notes/memos, 1995; 2 (Box 23)
      - Sonya correspondence, 2001 (Box 23)
      - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 23)
      - Scripts, notes, etc., 1992-2001; 22 (Box 23)
      - Scripts, notes, related papers, 1991-1995; 21 (Box 24)
    - A New Brain - scripts, notes, etc., 1996-1998; 18 (Box 25)
    - Passion
      - Scripts, notes, workshop material, etc., 1993-1994; 13 (Box 26)
      - Scripts, notes, workshop material, etc., 1993-1996; 17 (Box 27)
      - Outline in JL's hand, undated (Box 28)
      - Sondheim song ideas, undated (Box 28)
      - JL song dialogue, undated (Box 28)
      - Script, television version, undated (Box 28)
      - Photocopy of Fosca, undated (Box 28)
      - Additional final copy, 1994 (Box 28)
      - Post opening, 1994 (Box 28)
      - Preview opening, 1994; 4 (Box 28)
      - Drafts, 1994; 2 (Box 28)
      - Calendar, recording, 1994 (Box 29)
      - Novel, undated (Box 29)
      - Tony Awards, 1994 (Box 29)
      - Reviews, 1994 (Box 29)
      - Notes, 1993-11994 (Box 29)
      - Legal and budget, 1993-1994 (Box 29)
      - Research, undated (Box 29)
      - Contracts, 1995 (Box 29)
      - Press, 1994 (Box 29)
      - Opening, 1994 (Box 29)
      - Press kits, 1994 (Box 29)
      - Sondheim, 1994 (Box 29)
      - Workshop, 1992-1993 (Box 29)
      - Casting, 1992-1994 (Box 29)
      - Playbills, 1994; 3 (Box 29)
      - Scripts, related papers, 1993-1996; 15 (Box 30)
    - "The Royal Family" script, 1995 (Box 31)
    - Sight Unseen, undated; 5 (Box 32)
    - Note cards, undated (Box 31)
    - Sunday in the Park with George
      - Baldwin piano, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Cast, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Thank you notes [empty folder], undated (Box 31)
      - Letters to cast members, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Letters, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Rehearsal schedule, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Invites, 1993 (Box 31)
      - Costumes, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Theatre plans, St. James, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Jujamcyn offices, undated (Box 31)
      - Press memos, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Programs, playbills, 1994; 2 (Box 31)
      - Program, original production, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Concert material, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Projections, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Set, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Props, undated (Box 31)
      - Seat orders, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Bernadette Peters, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Photos, original production, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Photos, concert, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Miscellaneous, 1994; 2 (Box 31)
      - Clippings
        - New York Post, 1994 (Box 31)
        - New York Newsday, 1994 May 13 (Box 31)
        - [miscellaneous clippings], 1994 (Box 31)
        - North Jersey Herald, 1994 (Box 31)
        - Associated Press, 1994 (Box 31)
        - Backstage, 1994 (Box 31)
        - Daily News, 1994 May 2 (Box 31)
        - [miscellaneous clippings], 1994 (Box 31)
        - Daily News, 1994 (Box 31)
        - New York Magazine, 1994; 2 (Box 31)
        - New York Newsday, 1994; 2 (Box 31)
        - Miscellaneous clippings, 1994 (Box 31)
        - New York Times, 1994 May 12 (Box 31)
        - New York Post, 1994 Apr 8 (Box 31)
        - New Yorker, 1994 May 16 (Box 31)
        - Theatre Week, 1993 (Box 31)
        - Theatre Week, 1994 May (Box 31)
        - Theatrical Index, 1994 Apr 11 (Box 31)
        - Miscellaneous clippings, 1994 (Box 31)
      - Sondheim, 1994-1997 (Box 31)
      - Clippings, 1985 (Box 31)
      - Note cards, undated (Box 31)
      - Production book, 1983 (Box 31)
      - Script, 1983 (Box 31)
      - 1984, 1983-1984; 2 (Box 33)
      - Sondheim collaboration, undated (Box 33)
      - Workshop programs, 1983 (Box 33)
      - Photo following final performance, undated (Box 33)
      - Workshop version, act I, 1983 (Box 33)
      - Drafts, 1983; 2 (Box 33)
      - Franklin and Marshall commencement, 1985 (Box 33)
      - Antoinette Perry Award nomination, 1983-1984; 2 (Box 33)
      - Script, 1983 (Box 33)
      - Notes, undated (Box 33)
      - Notes, revisions, undated (Box 33)
      - Drafts and revisions, 1983-1984 (Box 33)
      - Drafts, 1984 (Box 33)
      - Cuts, 1983-1984 (Box 33)
      - Miscellaneous, 1983-1984; 5 (Box 33)
      - Script, 1983 (Box 33)
    - "Swing Time", 1996-1998; 2 (Box 34)
    - Table Settings, 1996 (Box 34)
    - "Tales of Manhattan", 1979; 2 (Box 34)
    - "Target Practice", 1995 (Box 34)
    - "Themes and Variations", 1995-1996; 2 (Box 34)
    - Twelve Dreams
      - Scripts, revisions, related papers, 1995-1996; 12 (Box 34)
      - Twelve Dreams published, 1982 (Box 35)
      - New York Shakespeare Festival reviews, 1981-1982 (Box 35)
      - Lincoln Center reviews, 1995-1996 (Box 35)
      - Lincoln Center artwork/note cards, undated (Box 35)
      - budget, 1995 (Box 35)
      - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 35)
      - Miscellaneous, 1986 Aug 2 (Box 35)
      - Incidental misc., 1981 (Box 35)
      - Script revised, 1986 Aug 8 (Box 35)
      - New York Shakespeare Festival reading, 1981 (Box 35)
      - Final clean script, 1982 (Box 36)
      - Miscellaneous, undated; 4 (Box 36)
      - Version A, 1981 Sep 23; 3 (Box 36)
      - Photocopy of revised version, 1978 (Box 36)
      - Revised title pages, 1986 Aug (Box 36)
      - Unbound completed draft, undated (Box 36)
      - Rough copy, 1977 Dec 1 (Box 36)
      - 1978 Oct (Box 36)
      - Outline, 1977 (Box 36)
      - Complete draft, 1978 Mar (Box 36)
      - Photocopy of complete draft, 1981 Dec 31 (Box 36)
      - Programs, 1995 (Box 37)
    - Who's on Top, 1998-1999; 14 (Box 37)
    - Who's on Top, 1996-2000; 12 (Box 38)
  - Assorted Scripts
    - Photograph, 1977-1979; 4 (Box 39)
    - The Last Resort, 1981 (Box 39)
    - In Stitches, undated (Box 39)
    - Spring Awakening by Janet Sternburg, undated. (Box 39)
    - A Funny Thing by Janet Sternburg, undated (Box 39)
    - "Pastchen's Lost plays" by Janet Sternburg, undated (Box 39)
    - Awake in Spain by Janet Sternburg, undated (Box 39)
    - Miscellaneous by Janet Sternburg, undated; 2 (Box 39)
    - Table Settings, 1979-1981; 4 (Box 39)
    - Will and Testaments Gallery, 1978; 2 (Box 39)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, undated; 2 (Box 39)
  - Other Papers
    - Articles, photos, etc., 1974-2005; 22 (Box 40)
    - Lois Kivesto dissertation, 2001; 2 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence, 1985-2006; 6 (Box 41)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 42)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 42)
    - Retired files (Box 42)
      - Readers' reports, 1993-1996 (Box 42)
      - General, 1993-1995; 3 (Box 42)
      - Photograph, 1979 (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous, 1984-1993 (Box 42)
      - Personal, 1963-1988 (Box 42)
      - "Friends Indeed", 1994 (Box 42)
      - Paul Gemignani, 1994 (Box 42)
      - Invoices to be paid, 1994 (Box 42)
      - Orchestra, 1994 (Box 42)
      - Other, 1994 (Box 42)
      - Mandy Patinkin, 1994 (Box 42)
      - Contact sheets, 1984-1994 (Box 42)
      - Cut-outs, 1994 (Box 42)
      - Retired files, 1995-1997 (Box 42)
    - Proposed budgets for Muscle workshops, 1995-1997 (Box 43)
    - Passion house seats, 1994 (Box 43)
    - Retired files, 1993-1996 (Box 43)
    - Passion London, 1995-1996 (Box 43)
    - Passion TV tapes, 1994-1997; 3 (Box 43)
    - Retired files, 1993-1996 (Box 43)
    - Contracts, 1994-1995 (Box 43)
    - Retired files, 1992; 2 (Box 43)
    - Business correspondence, 1992-1995; 3 (Box 43)
    - Personal correspondence and call sheets, 1996; 4 (Box 43)
    - Call sheets, correspondence, travel, etc., 1992-1998; 9 (Box 44)
    - Call sheets, correspondence, travel, etc., 1993-1998; 6 (Box 44)
    - Call sheets, 1996 Jan-Dec; 2 (Box 44)
    - Letters sent by JL personal, 1992-1994; 2 (Box 44)
    - Production notebook, undated; 2 (Box 45)
    - Falsettos, production notebook, undated (Box 45)
    - Table Settings, production notebook, undated (Box 45)
    - Midsummer Night's Dream, production notebook, undated (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980-1985; 2 (Box 45)
    - New York Shakespeare Festival Benefit, 1992 (Box 45)
    - Falsettos, miscellaneous material, 1990-1992; 3 (Box 45)
    - Merrily We Roll Along, miscellaneous material, 1980-1988; 6 (Box 45)
    - Volunteers, 1994 (Box 45)
    - Press clippings, 1977-1996; 9 (Box 46)
    - Press clippings, 1977-1996; 8 (Box 46)
  - Audiovisual Material
    Boxes 47-50 and 63 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Videocassettes
      Restricted Fragile Material.